We're at the illegal internet cafe!
Everyone, pull yourself together!
Lead the way.
LAVISH GIFTS, GENEROUS FREEBIES
LIANG LIANG COMPUTER SUPPLIES
All of them. Take them away!
Get up! Move!
Hurry up! Move!
Hold on. This is a misunderstanding.
You've made a mistake.
We have all the required licenses.
This is a legit internet cafe. Hold on.
This is a misunderstanding.
-Hold on.
-Are you the boss?
This is an important suspect.
Take him away.
No.
Mr. He, I'm just helping out.
Help me! Help me!
Why are you taking all these people back?
Are these people related to the case?
He Yuanhang.
Are you sober?
Listen carefully.
The Special Task Force is in charge here.
You are an unrelated person.
Go back and rest.
-Why should I?
-Dad,
this is an investigation scene.
Don't cause any trouble.
Whose side are you on?
Officer, two days ago,
the trolley for moving stocks was stolen.
-Are you going to help us?
-Go to the police station.
We're from the criminal department.
-You are all police officers.
-Go away.
You've forgotten your true mission.
You have forgotten where you came from.
Everyone!
Search every corner
using Captain Ran's Tremaux Algorithm.
Don't miss anything,
not even a screw! You hear me?
Tremaux Algorithm? You?
Officer! You're framing me!
-I'm innocent! Officer!
-Zheng Zhong!
Put that man with the hood in my car!
Hurry!
-Captain Qu.
-What is it?
Which car am I getting on?
Han Zi'ang's case is investigated
by the Special Task Force now.
You are no longer needed.
Send your father home.
Let's go.
PUBLIC SECURITY
Understood.
Yes.
I'll surely complete this mission.
Goodbye, sir.
I just received orders
from the city council.
The case of the four
teenagers' disappearance
will be investigated
by the Nanshan Branch.
With Han Zi'ang's case,
it is…
It is now…
FOUR MISSING TEENAGERS CASE
FIVE MISSING TEENAGERS CASE
…Five Teenagers Case.
Captain Qu, they are looking for you.
Go downstairs and take a look.
Dad, calm down.
I've accepted the decision
not to be in the Special Task Force.
-I won't accept it!
-He Yuanhang.
Do you know what this place is?
Qu Dahai.
Xiaohe contributed to the case.
Why can't she join the task force?
He Yuanhang,
merging the case is a decision
made by the superiors.
Besides, Xiaohe has never been
a part of the task force.
The case involves the kidnapping
of teenagers now.
She experienced something similar,
so she isn't fit to join the task force.
Who are you to decide that?
She is Ran's direct apprentice.
Not trusting her
means you are not trusting Ran.
How dare you mention Captain Ran?
Back then,
if you hadn't burdened
Captain Ran excessively
by letting him take care
of the whole family,
would that have happened to him?
-What?
-How dare you
still mention Captain Ran's name
around here?
I'm telling you.
You are responsible for his death!
-What?
-What's going on?
We can't stop him…
What's wrong? Dad! Dad!
Tonight at 7:30 p.m. Beijing Time,
the 2002 World Cup match
kicks off between China and Brazil.
Testing, silly testing…
IMPROVING SALES
MANAGING RISKS FOR WIN-WIN SITUATIONS
ANPING INSURANCE, PROTECT YOUR SAFETY
The times are progressing.
Even our football team
has qualified for the World Cup.
How can we still slack?
We need to change our mindset
and the way we speak.
Come and tell everyone
what our core competency is.
Do we even have any?
We're just eating, drinking,
and entertaining our clients.
Also, we lose money.
What's so funny?
I've trained you all for half a year
and you have retained nothing.
You're the fool who knows nothing.
Gosh.
Stand up.
Turn.
Anping Insurance.
-Protects your safety.
Seriously, you're the security team.
Why didn't you submit
the property owner's lost camera?
You even used it to take random pictures.
All of you will be in trouble
if the property owner reports
it to the police.
I asked them to take the pictures.
Those are all pictures of the scene.
I want to keep it as evidence.
The police often do this
when they investigate a case.
Shut up!
Do you really think
you are working as a police officer
after assisting them for a few days?
Don't forget who your boss is
in Yuanlongli.
Officer Ran.
Welcome.
How can I help you?
Mr. Qian,
what has Wu Shanlong of Unit 1703
been up to recently in Yuanlongli?
Him?
He usually helps the management body out
by doing electrical work
and fixing internet cables
on a part-time basis.
He's just trying to make a living.
His charges are cheap.
Most of the time, he helps us for free.
Wu Shanlong has a fetish.
He can't have intercourse,
but he likes to keep women's garments
and peek at women's bodies from afar.
For some reason,
I've always felt a gaze at midnight.
It creeps me out.
We live in 1713.
The clothes I hung out to dry
and my shoes at the door
were all stolen by him.
We complained to management,
but Qian Dajun didn't even care.
Everyone else in the building
couldn't run any business here.
He forced them out.
Can I borrow this?
Go ahead.
By my guest.
Thank you.
Officer Ran, let me send you off.
Take care.
ANPING INSURANCE, PROTECT YOUR SAFETY
1997?
Back then,
Mr. Jin met Wu Shanlong
and wanted to change his business.
In the end, he started a gambling den.
Later, the gambling den
was raided by the police.
Mr. Jin ran away.
He is still missing right now.
I was just a lackey who helped out.
I was jailed for two years.
Isn't it too much for me, Officer He?
It had nothing to do with me.
What was the relationship
between Wu Shanlong
and the father and daughter
who went missing in 1997?
I don't know.
I only interacted with Wu Shanlong once.
However,
Wu Shanlong did go to find Wolf.
He wanted Wolf to help him kill
those two people.
However, Wolf failed.
Later, Wu Shanlong said
he went and did the deed himself.
He said that himself?
Yes. He said it himself.
I swear I'm not lying.
Ran, you scared me. It's so late at night.
Didn't you say you felt
someone's gaze at night?
Ran, you're scaring me.
Keep quiet.
Go inside,
turn off the lights,
and open the curtains.
Leave the door open for me.
Come.
HE
Hey.
I have got something huge.
Jin Manshan's lackey can prove
that Wu Shanlong said
he did the deed himself.
Wu Shanlong killed Xu Meng and her father?
That's right.
What's the situation over there?
I found a secret camera
at New York Block Unit 415.
I suspect it was Wu Shanlong
who installed it.
That punk.
He tried to harm Qiao?
Well, gather the evidence.
I'll rush over immediately.
We must catch him red-handed.
All right.
Sorry.
-Seriously? I was watching a show!
-What the hell?
This stupid management body.
What are they doing?
-A blackout?
-I don't even know what's going on.
-What are they doing?
-So annoying.
Qian Dajun!
Officer Ran.
I can only cut the power
-for ten minutes at most.
-Shush.
Got it.
The match of the century will begin soon.
If the residents can't watch
the match, my head will roll.
-Hurry up.
-I understand.
Ran, be careful.
Ran!
Ran, install the camera again.
You're spooking the culprit.
Those property management imbeciles.
Why aren't they picking up?
Qian!
I'm going to dig up your ancestor's grave!
I risked my reputation
to work with all of you.
Shut up.
What is your kid doing again?
-Why are you…
-Shush.
He, should we call the police station
and request backup?
No need.
It'll only cause more trouble.
Let's deal with this quickly.
Good idea.
A reminder.
I have to restore the power
in two minutes.
Ran.
We also want to help.
We'll beat the pervert up!
-Yes.
-Exactly. Beat him to death.
Help Ma Qiang and Wang Xinglong
guard the elevator and door
on the first floor.
If you see Wu Shanlong,
don't force yourself,
and call me immediately.
All right.
Wu, are you inside?
The municipality was relocating
the utility lines just now.
Someone's electricity meter
short-circuited.
I came by to check.
Is he inside the room?
Wu Shanlong! Police! Open the door!
DOUBLE FISH
He.
It's warm. He just left.
Walkie-talkie.
Ma Qiang.
Do you see Wu Shanlong?
Sir, I didn't see him. No.
Qiao, do you see Wu Shanlong over there?
Ran, we didn't see him, either.
Wu Shanlong might be
in the underground parking lot.
Ran, take the elevator
and go outside. Intercept him
at the parking lot entrance.
I'll go after him using the stairs.
We'll corner him.
Is there anything I can help with?
YUANLONGLI INTERNATIONAL GARDEN
Get lost.
Wu Shanlong!
Stop!
What the heck?
Is this his car?
He! He's here!
I've locked the door to the stairs!
Are there any more exits?
The parking lot entrance.
The parking lot entrance
was opened last week!
He might be able to exit from there!
Stop!
Catch him!
Move! Move!
Move!
What are you doing?
He went that way!
After him!
He!
Quick, call an ambulance!
Stay awake, He!
He!
The steel rod pierced his lung
and broke his rib.
Thankfully, Officer He is lucky.
A few centimeters above,
and it'd have pierced his heart.
The consequences could've been worse.
You must do your best to treat him.
There mustn't be any complications.
He is the hero of the police force.
Don't worry.
Thank you.
Sir!
Are you all right, sir?
He.
He. Are you all right, He?
FOLDER
-Be careful.
Dad.
I'm fine.
Are you really fine?
I said I'm fine.
Anyway, He,
why did you suddenly think
of bringing Xiaohe
to Yuanlongli's internet cafe
to search for clues?
Ran brought us there.
Ran.
Don't just stand there.
Tell everyone about it.
No way.
Yes.
Did you hear what he just said?
I… What did he just say?
Stop playing dumb.
He was scolding you.
He said you were biased towards Qu Dahai.
Xiaohe found the lead,
but you gave Qu Dahai the case
and even stopped Xiaohe
from joining the task force.
Is the criminal department
trying to steal credit too?
Captain,
I did it for Xiaohe's sake.
Wasn't Xiaohe kidnapped
when she was a child?
I was afraid that she
might relive those memories
after joining the task force.
What if it triggered… What you call it…
Hush. I can't hear him.
You hear that?
He's scolding you.
Are you talking to me?
Captain Ran said
the internet cafe owner you arrested
wasn't a kidnapping suspect.
You are only wasting your time
by interrogating him.
Also, Ran taught you
the Tremaux Algorithm.
Shouldn't you provide guidance
to Xiaohe now?
Dad,
you've had a long day.
Let's go home.
Uncle Ran still has a train to catch.
He Xiaohe.
Yes.
As long as you won't affect
the Special Task Force's investigation,
I will give you special permission
to assist in the investigation
of Han Zi'ang's case.
However, you must report all your actions
to the team leader of the task force.
Thank you, Captain.
-Hold on…
-Enough.
Captain, many parents are outside.
I'm warning you. Don't pull
this trick often in the future.
Train harder
if you want to outwit me.
CRIMINAL DEPARTMENT OFFICE
He.
He. You're awake.
-Let me call a doctor.
-Wait. There's no rush.
Water.
Right away.
How's that?
Here.
Brat,
are you trying to scald me?
Let me add some cold water.
No need.
-Then, I'll go and find a doctor.
-Wait.
Talk to me about the case.
Where's Wu Shanlong?
He was pierced by steel rods
and couldn't be resuscitated. He is dead.
The people in the forensic department
found a small amount
of human bone samples
in the bathroom's drain.
After examination,
it matches the DNA
found on Xu Zhihong's hair
collected at Xu's apartment.
Moreover,
the skin samples found in the blue heels
also match Xu Meng's DNA.
Combined with Wu Zhengxiong's
and Hu Anping's testimony…
In 1997, Wu Shanlong
hired Wolfie to murder someone.
Wu Shanlong said
he went and did the deed himself.
We can basically confirm
that Wu Shanlong is the murderer
of Xu Meng and her father.
Are there any accomplices?
None has been found at the moment.
What about the motive?
According to the information
we have currently,
my guess is that Wu Shanlong
had a strong urge to control women
due to his physiological defect.
He visited the foot massage parlor
frequently with Song Qingsong.
He had his eyes on Xu Meng
and wanted her to himself.
MUSE FOOT MASSAGE
After Song Qingsong decided
to hire him to murder the victims,
Wu Shanlong lied
and used Wolfie as a scapegoat.
He then purposely helped
Xu Meng and her father
to disappear to escape debt.
Xu Meng thought Wu Shanlong
helped her out of kindness.
To her surprise, he was actually trying
to take her by force
after she successfully escaped.
Wu Shanlong faced resistance
from Xu Meng and her father,
and he was afraid of Song Qingsong
finding out about his plan.
In the end,
he killed them both.
Unfortunately,
we couldn't find Xu Meng's body.
NANSHAN BRANCH
BUILDING NO. 1, INPATIENT DEPARTMENT
Xiaohe.
Xiaohe!
Mrs. He,
you're right on time.
He just woke up.
Take a seat.
Xiaohe.
I've not seen you for ages.
You've lost weight.
You are in such bad shape.
It's fine.
Just a minor wound.
Xiaohe,
I've achieved something huge this time.
The criminal used a steel rod this long
to stab me at this place,
and I didn't even let out a groan.
I even beat up the criminal.
So you risked your life
just to achieve something.
You are no longer young.
In the future,
you must take good care of yourself.
I've talked to you about this.
DIVORCE AGREEMENT
Our marriage has become like this
for a while now.
It's bad for everyone if this goes on.
Why not just let it go
and end it cleanly?
Actually, I've been trying to talk
to you about this.
But I've been busy with the investigation.
Give me a pen.
HUSBAND'S SIGNATURE
WIFE'S SIGNATURE: SUN YUN
What's wrong?
CUSTODY OF THE CHILD, HE XIAOHE
GOES TO THE WIFE
I'll soon transfer
to the provincial headquarters.
I'll bring Xiaohe with me.
This is better for her.
Look at you right now.
How can you even take care of her?
Xiaohe is becoming more rebellious now.
If she stays here,
it won't be too long
until she goes astray.
You don't need to pay alimony.
I can support her on my own.
If you miss her,
you may visit her at any time.
I won't stop you.
Do you hear me?
He Yuanhang.
He Yuanhang!
I don't object to the divorce.
We all want to seek happiness,
and I have nothing to say about that.
Don't use me as an excuse in the future.
I'm sick of hearing,
"It's for Xiaohe's sake."
I'll decide how I live my life.
I'm not going to the provincial capital.
Xiaohe. The adults are talking.
Don't cause any trouble.
The adults also shouldn't cause
any trouble for the child.
The schools in the provincial capital
are so much better
than the ones in Weiyang.
Attending university or studying abroad
will be so much easier in the future.
Don't you like music?
England. The United States. France.
No matter where you want to go,
I'll also support you.
I don't need anyone to decide for me.
He Xiaohe. I am your guardian.
As long as you are still a minor,
you need my consent
before you make your decisions.
This is non-negotiable.
If that's the case,
it's also non-negotiable for me.
I'm following Dad.
Look at her. She's really stubborn,
just like you.
She won't be able to turn good.
CUSTODY OF THE CHILD, HE XIAOHE
GOES TO THE HUSBAND
HUSBAND'S SIGNATURE: HE
What is it? You don't want her to leave?
Xiaohe, I have raised an amazing daughter.
-Give me a hug.
-Don't be so full of yourself.
Not leaving with Mom
has nothing to do with you.
What do you mean?
My friends, my band,
and my rock career are all in Weiyang.
Listen now.
Leave me alone in the future.
But I am your only parent now.
You don't agree?
Mom just left.
I'll call her back right away.
I agree.
Take good care of yourself.
I still have lessons in the afternoon.
Family is a strange thing.
If the family is intact,
people dig it
until there's a hole.
If it isn't intact,
people will do their best to repair it.
They will even
do something as stupid
as repairing a golden bowl
with a piece of tile.
What is it?
Take a guess.
No.
CERTIFICATE OF HONOR
"In the June 30th case,
Officer He Yuanhang demonstrated
keen investigative thinking,
exceptional judgment,
a strong sense of responsibility,
and extensive investigative experience.
He made significant contributions
in solving the case.
To commend his exemplary performance
and promote integrity,
in accordance
with the People's Police Rewards
and Punishments Regulations,
it is submitted to the Provincial
Public Security Department
that Officer He Yuanhang should be awarded
a second-class individual merit."
The police station specifically
requested me to give it to you in person.
SECOND-CLASS MERIT MEDAL
OF THE MINISTRY OF PUBLIC SECURITY OF PRC
NAME: HE YUANHANG
MEDAL: SECOND-CLASS MERIT
I get custody of my daughter
and the second-class merit.
Let's see
who dares call me
a good-for-nothing again.
What are you doing?
I'm not done admiring it.
Once you recover,
you must take your medications
for your condition on time.
It's time to quit drinking cola.
The same goes for cigarettes,
alcohol, and fatty meat.
-The doctor even mentioned to--
-Enough.
Stop nagging beside me. All right?
You're so annoying.
Go back and keep working, Deputy Captain.
He.
If you didn't push me away,
I'd probably be the one lying here now.
I told you not to nag. All right?
Do you think I did it for you?
I did it for myself.
If I let my apprentice get hurt,
it'll only make me look bad
as your mentor.
It shows how incapable I am.
Go away.
Don't disturb my rest.
I'm leaving,
sir.